

Tristan DeAugustine

Full-Stack Software Developer

Experienced Developer from Anna Maria Island with a demonstrated history of working hard and dedicating time to my passion for code. Strong engineering professional with a Full Stack Software Development focused in Front End from Suncoast Developers Guild. Aside from software development you can probably find me writing music or spending time with my friends and family.

deaugustinetristan@gmail.com

941-720-7443

5961 35th avenue n, St Petersburg, United States

WORK EXPERIENCE

Teachers Assistant Suncoast Developers Guild

10/2019 - Present

Full-Stack software developer bootcamp Achievements/Tasks

- Creating SPA applications that are mobile first design with Front end and Back end.

Software Support

Accusoft

03/2020 - Present

Tampa, Florida

St Petersburg

Accusoft is a software development company specializing in content processing, conversion, and automation. We enable users to solve content challenges

Achievements/Tasks

- Problem solving bugs and errors that come in from our internal database or code
- Writing C# and SQL queries to accomplish tasks at hand
- Reproducing issues to help better determine the cause of the problem.

Camp Counselor **Bostocks Martial Arts**

06/2017 - 09/2018 Martial Arts Dojo

Bradenton, Florida

Achievements/Tasks

- Helped oversee 25+ kids on public outings
- Trained kids in Taekwando
- Taught kids aged 4-12 life morals and responsibility

EDUCATION

Full Stack Developer bootcamp Suncoast Developers Guild

07/2019 - 10/2019

St Petersburg, Florida

High School Education IMG Academy

06/2018 - 01/2019

Bradenton, Florida

SKILLS

HTML

CSS

JavaScript

React .Net

C#

Postgres

SOL

Vue

PROJECTS

Weather App 🗹

Working weather app pulling from external API (React)

Productivity Suite 🗹

Multifunction SPA application that allows you to keep track and mark important events in calendar, keep track of thoughts and notes in journal based on color coordination, and use the To-Do list to keep track of your day to day tasks. (HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, C#, .Net,

Employee Database 🗹

Employee Database app using external API to hold and store information. (React)

Recipe Website 🗹

Useful website for getting healthy recipes to cook with.

Portfolio Website 🗹

 Portfolio Website to get linked to all of my important links such as github, LinkedIn.

INTERESTS

Software Development

Reading Books

Working out

Football

Sinaina

Music

Playing Guitar